Thank you for watching
ME
Boobershi: Here's what happened behind the scenes and out in the open 2023
me Tonight, continuing from the previous episode, we will look back on the various events that took place during the midsummer national tour.
We'll continue tonight with a look back at the various events that took place during the midsummer national tour, including videos taken by the members.
First of all, I'd like to introduce a small surprise that the members bought and did on the spot.
I didn't know...
I wonder if they're only here now...
Wow! Oh, shit!
- Wow! Arthur! What?
- Kiichi, you totally...
Wow!
That's good.
Sorry.
I wrote it wrong... but it's cute.
Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
It's so simple and fun to do this!
Next is Yumiki's mysterious challenge to put a cup on the target's head without being noticed
what the heck is this?
Kitchen
Oh, I did something like this
And listen to this
What is it?
We did it together.
And back here.
Check here, here, here.
Here. There you go.
Nana's cute.
You're my dumpling brother, so stand up in front of me.
And I'm going to go up.
Do it.
Tell me what you're gonna do.
Do the "hee" thing.
I'll crop that picture for you later.
Thank you.
You didn't notice.
I didn't notice.
I see.
So that's why Yumiki's doing the cup-topping challenge on her own.
I have a favor to ask.
Let's do it here.
Oh, no.
Why?
Congratulations!
Amazing.
Surprisingly many kisses
Congratulations!
Cups on top.
I haven't decided at all
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You're lucky.
Then we'll decide together.
Okay.one, two, three, four, five...
blue sky
I was able to take a picture with my junior
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, YUUPPI!
And Ogawa set up a challenge for the seniors to pretend to pour water from a glass with no water in it!
Delicious!
So sweet!
We're just talking a little bit.
Oh no!
I like the relationship between people and convenience stores.
It'd be fun to call it that.
I don't think so.
Congratulations!
You're right.
You're going to throw it?
Wow.
Bullshit.
What a lie
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
How did you fall?
Oh, my God.
how did you what?
Next, Yumiki and Seimiya set up a fight surprise.
Umezawa's reaction to the surprise fight that Yumiki and Seimiya set up.
Surprise!
To Umezawa
How did you like it?How was it?
Nagoya
First day
But it's like this.
I felt a sense of relief that we had come this far
and the mixed feeling of having come this far
But I had a lot of fun today.
We're fighting in the back.
In a good way.
Why did you do that?
Wait a minute.
The guy from Eurp...
I don't know how you can say that.
I can't.
No?
Well, that's realistic.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I'm gonna cry.
I didn't say that.
Hey, hey, hey.
I don't like this
I don't know how to say it
what are you talking about?
That's unusual.
What do you mean you didn't?
I can't cry.
That feels good.That feels good.
I didn't say that.
You didn't say it, and then you said it later.
If I cry...
Lee will stop it.
Good morning, ma'am.
Go upstairs.
Come on.
What the hell?
Surprise.
I didn't cry.
Yes, I did.
I have to tell them.
I have to tell her.
I have to take it apart.
I got it apart.
I've got to take it apart.
I got it.
Oh, my God, I'm crying.
What are you talking about?
We're fighting.
Would you stop it or not?
It was a surprise.
A fight.
Would you stop it for us?
From a different camera.
Yes, from behind the camera.
Thank you so much.
That's great.That's amazing.
I mean, Imin was really crying.
She really cried.
You believe that, don't you?
She's an actress.
But it was the first day.
I was trying too hard with my facial expressions.
I should have tried harder with words.
Because the way Yumiki said it was so messed up.
Yumiki's realistic, too.
I've never been in a fight that much either.
All I can say is "I can't".
I can't do it anymore.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you can't say that.
But you're good at it.
You really had me fooled.
It was a real surprise.
It was so real, I couldn't even stop myself from saying, "Stop, stop, stop.
Well, well, well.
That kind of thing happens quite often.
No, really.
There really isn't.
It was very difficult.
I told Mr. Umu that it was a surprise.
But I didn't tell the other members or the staff.
Who was around there?
Everyone was there.
I thought it was a real fight.
I thought it might be a really bad situation. I was really worried that it might be a bad situation.
I was really nervous.
Other people could have come to stop you.
Yes, and the staff, too.
There's a seabar that gives orders to the whole venue.
It's like Seimia and Yumiki are fighting with each other.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
If KAIRAN didn't stop them, they'd just keep fighting.
I don't know where that came from.
And then...
It's funny, isn't it?
It's so simple, it's a tradition.
He's an uncle.
Kawasaki's good.
Not at all.
There's a reason for this.
I saw the camera.
Over here.
I thought they were filming something.
I was crouching down and filming so that I wouldn't be seen.
I felt like I had to stay out of the way.
And I knew I shouldn't make a sound.
I followed the rules I set for myself.
So that I wouldn't get any reactions.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Poor senpai.
What's with the cups challenge? What's with the cups on top challenge?
It was just a prank by Yumiki.
Is that right? I was in Nagoya.
Nagoya is famous for its dumplings.
There are so many people wearing dumplings.
When I see a bun, I want to put a cup on it.
It makes me want to put a cup on it.
You didn't notice this Yuki?
I just found out.
Why don't you tell us about it?
I'm impressed.
Why didn't you tell us?
Then what did you do with it?
I took that one, too, when I did it.
That's great... for you to tell us here.
Great lyrics, Yumiki!
Why did you do that on your own?
They did a little bit of this kind of thing.
Various things...
Next Inoue, this way please.
Hurray for your brother!
Here's a picture of you at Jingu.
Me?
Yes.
I was there on the first day.
When I passed by on the trolley...
I thought I found you.
I didn't know what to do.
I asked him to do a banzai for me.
I'm sorry I made you aware of it.I'm sorry I put you on the spot.
You know... we're going this way now.
It's right in front of you.
That's why we're going north.
Not all of them come here.
But when it's right in front of you...
Inoue! Inoue!
Come here.
I felt like an unwelcome guest.
I thought I might have annoyed you.
I did? I'm happy to do whatever you want.
You're so sweet.
I'm flattered.
Oh, I want to see it.
What? It's from the show.
I see. You're filming it or you're a member?
I can move at such a distance.
Where are you?
Oh, that.
That's...
And here's a shot of you with the other members.
This is the one Mr. Nagao took.
Much closer.
Is this Yamashita?
It's like this.
Much closer.
Pumpkin.
I usually stand like this, but I get super excited when I'm close to a live performance.
Wow, here it comes! It's like...
What's that? It's Mansuya, isn't it? Huh? It's a munzuya.
I'm the one who just came from this side, right?
I was watching Mr. Nagao and the others, so Mr. Nagao was taking pictures of me.
But Mr. Nagao is an idiot.
He didn't take a picture of me.
After that, he just snapped, and I got a picture of him in his pocket all the time.
He's an old man, you know.
He was in his pockets the whole time.
That's why he said he didn't have the other side.
That's why I don't see what Inoue said.
I saw you doing the banzai with the transparency.
Oh, right.
Banzai is a clenched fist.
I was holding the microphone.
When I went there, they knew I was there to see the show.
So the people around me, they know that I'm here.
You know the encore? During the encore...
Nogizaka's encore?
They say "Nogizaka46" the whole time.
And for encore, you know, there's a little bit of time.
And they started saying my name.
I asked him... 46.
46.
It's a bit of a mix.
Like Osawa Mune.
Like Osawa Sou.
That's pretty good... in a big company.
I'm embarrassed.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, I'm embarrassed. Stop, stop, stop. It's embarrassing.
No, thanks, but...
Oh, there's a video.
There is a video.
Let's watch it.
Oh, Soukou Oosawa.
Oh, one more thing.
I watched only كلcha.
I haven't seen anything in a while...
A lot.
I'm not sure if it's hard to tell, but I was at third base, so...
I've been playing with you guys because I'm not busy, and you guys don't come out.
I'm glad you guys don't come out, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you!
I think this is Lilia's corner... it's good... and since this song was performed at one of every three shows on this year's national tour...
I'd like to see it.
I want to see it... is this a never-ending series?
Okay, let's go.
ematics
It's soup.
Mmm.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Kudo player, substantial by Shinji Yamaba
kena
[Applause]
Genius.
What the hell?
I've been calling you lately.
I'm here... on video.
Wait a minute.
He's totally talking Okinawa. Okinawa is totally talking.
Okinawa is where I'm from.
It was my first time to perform in Okinawa
It was my impulse.
And my hair is shisa hair.
No, no, no.
That's shisa hair.
Okinawa was Shisa hair.
I'm so happy.
You're saying...
It's like you're eating
Like you're eating it.
It's Hiroshima.
It's Hiroshima, so it's not momiji manju.
No, it's not.
You know where we had it?
It's a heart.
It's not as detailed as before.
You don't do "bang, bang, bang" as much as you used to.
I see.
Before, it was more like, "Woong, woong, ahang...
Like, "Woong-kyun-ba-kyun.
You had a lot of them scattered around.
I think it would be easier to understand.
It was just an idea that came to me at the time.
It's like, "Let's call him.
Let's call him.
You just did it.
I'll type first. I'll hit it first.
You were hitting it, Bacun.
You hit it, look at it, and then call him.
I'm a hit man.
I'm done.
Oh, my God, he's a hit man.
He's always right in front of me, like, diagonally across the street.
He's always right in front of you.
That's right.
I wonder what he'll do.
It's really great.
At the rehearsal for the first performance.
Until now, when the lights went out...
It's kind of the end of the show.
But when I turn around, it's over.
I'm going to turn around.
You made it all backwards.
That's why we started this, because it's not over.
That's not true.
They wouldn't turn off the lights when I was done.
I turn my head back.
Then I knew it was the end.
I learned that it's okay.
I've learned.
I'm going to be late.
When it's over, it's over.
How far can you go?
I want them to eat the local food.
Yeah, that's right.
But that's a hand mic. But that's a hand mic.
That's right.
It's originally posed like this.
You can't use this part.
It only works here.
This world
I can eat things I can pick up with my fingers.
Sushi and
You could use a spoon for this, too.
You can eat takoyaki (octopus dumplings)
You can eat takoyaki
That's fine, that's fine.
No problem at all.
I have a feeling this is it.
I even started to use this one.
But there's a lot of pressure to get attention here, isn't there?
Every time.
"What should we do?
I don't know what to do.
I'm calling them, like I'm losing my mind.
Like, "I want to quit.
I don't know what to say.
What are you talking about?
Why don't you just recruit them?
For fans.
It would be a lot of fun if we were doing that.
Sure, if there's something you'd like us to do...
I'd be happy to come over there.
Send it to me.
Now, on to the next item on the list... Sakira. Now then, what's next on the docket?
What? A real role.
You played a real role?
It's no secret that you and I are in love.
One-sidedly.
We've grown even closer on this tour.
The first was when we were at Jingu Park and Sakira put her hair in a ponytail.
She doesn't do much with her hair, so I was very happy to see her do it.
I also happened to be wearing a ponytail that day.
We had the same hair style.
I guess it's fate that a miracle and a miracle coincided on this amazing day.
Hey, Sakira!
Okay, ponytail and...
The second song was called "Ai (Love)" and we ran from the center stage to the B stage.
The second song was "Love" and they ran from the center stage to the back stage called "B stage".
Sakira was waiting for me with her arms outstretched.
She was waiting for me with her arms outstretched and told me to come jump into her heart.
It was the right thing to do.
It was for me.
So I jumped in.
I jumped in.
That's great!
That's what I'm talking about.
If you can get excited...
That's all I heard.
The third was in Aichi, where Sakira was from.
Her parents were there.
They greeted her here.
So you're already engaged.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Your parents are officially engaged, right, Sakira?
Engaged?
Hey...
Congratulations!
Thank you.
For talking to us.
He told my parents I'm a yakubo.
They ignored you.
His mother said how cute he was and how glad she was that he came.
She was so happy that you came.
I'd like to visit my parents again.
I want to.
She doesn't want to go.
I don't mind.
But she doesn't hate it as much as she used to.
I guess this tour has brought us closer.
But earlier backstage, Yakubo asked Sakira to sit next to him.
She refused.
You're right... don't get too deshabbatious.
What's with this world?
What's the end of the story?
Ichinose no Ai
Ichinose no Ai... what does this mean?
Yakubo's not happy.
They're in a relationship.
This is the opening of a regional show.
He's waiting in front of and behind Ichinose Miku.
That's why they're so close.
I parted my bangs for the first time at the Miyagi show. I parted my bangs for the first time at the Miyagi concert.
I don't usually wear my hair in this way, and I never change it.
I was really anxious about it.
She said it looked really good and cute on me.
Miku also asked me if I wanted her to wear a ponytail.
She told me she wanted me to wear a ponytail.
I remember saying it was Eichi's fault.
I remember... she was so cute.
I thought I was going to throw up.
It was so gross.
There was just so much cuteness.
I'm so short on words right now.
I don't know why I'm puking all of a sudden.
You didn't tell me I was too cute.
But you told me that's why I did the ponytail.
That's part of it, and part of it is because Miku said she wanted to see it.
Wait a minute... Yakubo's been in trouble.
It wasn't a miracle.
Ichinosei asked me to do something for him.
I told him I want to see him with a ponytail too.
But I also want to see it tied up.
I told her I wanted to see it tied up, and I told her she looked really pretty with her bangs parted.
She told me that too, and Miku told me the same thing, so...
Yakubo's aka didn't get it.
It's your fault.
I didn't get it.
There's still something in there, isn't there?
And can I touch your ass, Miku?
I said, "Can I touch your ass?
What do you mean, Ichinosei asked Endo if he could touch her ass? What do you mean, Ichinosei asked Endo if it was okay if he touched my butt?
That's right.
I'm probably really uncomfortable... and I don't even remember the whole thing.
That sounds like a molester's excuse.
What's that?
But I remember touching him.
That's why I told you before you said it, and you said it was okay.
I said, "Just once.
That's amazing.
You're so mature.
There's a V.
There's V.
Let's watch V.
What the hell is that?
Touching my ass during the show.
I mean during the show.
It's hard to say no when you're on the air.
It's not fair to say it on the set, Yakubo.
It's not fair.
I've never touched it either.
I'm a man of discretion, after all.
That's right.
I'm still aware that this is a body catcher's place.
But Ichinosei has already crossed that line and gotten permission.
Ichinosei, you're early.
But this tour was only for junior members.
As a senior, I think I need to get more involved with the juniors.
Wow, Endo, you're already thinking like that.
If it's okay with my ass, let's get along.
It's the same kind of thinking as the black guy. This is the same idea as the black guy.
Let's get to know each other by using our butts and stuff.
But it's not easy going from junior to senior.
Nick basically has a complete ass of maybe 5 kilos.
That's why he's starting to reach out to the seniors.
What kind of butt do you want to touch?
Because they can't touch it.
I mean, it's just normal.
They don't touch it, so I'm going to touch it.
But honestly, I want to touch it.
I want to touch it.
That's true, but you've already said that.
Don't make me say that.
Which one is it?
Of course we all want to touch it.
I don't think so.
To be honest, I think everyone has a secret.
I try not to hold back.
You represented us.
Well, then...
And you're saying something else.
I touched Tamura-san, too.
So there's someone else you're after?
You should've told us by now.
Matsuo-san?
Matsuo-san doesn't have the right image.
It seems like a high bar.
It's a high bar.
Are you okay? I'll say no.
You'll get turned down. See? They'll say no.
Of course they do.
If you say so first, I'll feel a sense of accomplishment when it's done.
I hate him.
You have a strong mentality.
I'll keep an eye on him.
I'm not interested in your rivals.
This time... at Jingu.
You know, I've been doing this for a long time.
You guys always say that when I get excited.
This time it suddenly got interesting.
Why do I say "you guys" to younger girls?
"You guys" to younger girls...
"Oh, you can't get excited?
She said, "You can't even speak yet.
And they're like, "Wow!
It's kind of funny.
They're not the kind of girls who would say something like that.
But the group is like, "Shiraishi!
They say "you guys", so now it's Yamashita.
You guys even had your first boyfriend.
You guys.
It's a tradition.
I was always like, "You guys"... but now I'm like, "You guys".
It's not a given.
I got bored and was wondering what to do.
Asuka told me to say "you guys".
That's right, Asuka-chan is one of you guys!
That's why it's a tradition.That's why it's a tradition.
That's why the kids who look like they're going to grow up a little bit say...
You guys!
It makes me happy to hear "you guys".
But it's easier to get people excited about it when it's you guys.
I'll get in on it too.
You know...
I get it.
If it's everyone, it's everyone
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I know, I know, I know
Next time, the biggest singing competition in history begins!
This is Minami Umezawa. Thank you for watching.
If you haven't subscribed to my channel yet, please do so.
Nyan!
Bye bye!